celtictiger.ie 2019-05-20

# Terms & Conditions, Privacy Policy, Warranty

1\. Subject matter  
HHO FACTORY, LTD (IRELAND) sold the customer (hereinafter "customer") in print catalogs, flyers and the online store specified goods to the following delivery and sales conditions (AGB).  

2\. Contract  
The contract between the customer and HHO FACTORY, LTD only comes through an order of the customer and its acceptance by the HHO FACTORY, LTD about. The customers order made via the Internet. HHO FACTORY, LTD accepts the order by the customer (a) an order confirmation (by email or mail) or transmitted (b) deliver the ordered goods (including delivery).  

3\. Product range  
Any details about the goods which the customer during the ordering process is not binding. In particular, changes in design and technology, which improve the functionality of a product, as well as errors in descriptions, illustrations, and pricing. All technical information on individual products is based on information provided by the manufacturer and are mandatory in this framework.  

4\. Payment Terms  
All catalog prices are guide prices which are continuously adjusted to the market. You are in Euro €, Including VAT, Unpackaged. Transportation and packaging costs are calculated separately. Payment must be paid net within 10 days after invoicing. New customers can purchase only against bank check, or cash advance. HHO FACTORY, LTD (IRELAND) reserves the right to sell to existing customers through these buying opportunities.  

4a. Cancellation  
We charge only 3.4% Pay with a credit or debit card fees for cancellation and processing fee for the case of a cancellation. you accept these terms with the agreement of this order  

5\. Conditions  
The ordered products can be shipped to an address in the European Union. Where to camp, the products will be delivered immediately to the address specified by the customer. Otherwise, a written order confirmation is done with the expected delivery date. The delivery of the goods takes place from (loading dock) at the expense and risk of the customer, even if partial deliveries. The claims made for externally visible damage to the goods ordered only against a certificate issued by a carrier.  

6\. Retention of title  
The delivered goods remain the property until full payment of HHO FACTORY, LTD. This may make a corresponding entry in the title register. If the customer with the payment of the purchase price is in default HHO FACTORY, LTD is entitled to rescind the contract (withdrawal) and the goods in their possession to take.  

7\. Defects Warranty and Liability  
For all products offered in the catalog, the guarantee period is 24 months from the date of purchase, unless a different warranty period is expressly stated. As far as the law permits are excluded, the liability for compensation. In particular, HHO FACTORY, LTD Engine Carbon Cleaner not be liable for any damages caused by improper use or natural wear and tear or for damage not caused to the item itself consequential damages. Deposit is not refundable!  

8\. Intellectual property

HHO FACTORY, LTD (IRELAND EUROPE) reserves for every design, text, graphics before any on their website, all rights reserved. Copying or other reproductions of the entire website or parts of this website is only permitted for the purpose of placing an order with HHO FACTORY, LTD. To illustrations, drawings, calculations and other documents provided to HHO FACTORY, LTD against the property and copyrights. Before their HHO FACTORY, LTD to third parties, the customers express written consent of HHO FACTORY, LTD.  

9\. Privacy -HHO FACTORY, LTD assured in the collection, processing and use of personal data, the provisions of the Irish Data Protection Act and the relevant legal standards to be observed. The occasion of order processing, customer data generated are used solely for internal market research. A transfer to third-party partner organizations will occur only when the proper delivery of services (order processing) is mandatory. The customer agrees to this use of his data. Moreover, he has available on request at any time the right to use the data stored about him and to prohibit their use for internal market research purposes.

10\. Jurisdiction and Applicable Law  
Jurisdiction is the seat of HHO FACTORY, LTD. The contract shall be governed by Irish law.  

11\. Final Provisions  
When selling in print catalogs, flyers and the online store are solely those of the HHO FACTORY, LTD goods specified in terms of their effect at the time of each contract is signed. These terms and conditions are particularly valid where they differ from those of the customers should be. For the delivery of software is also attached to the disk and/or information contained in this License Agreement by the manufacturer. By opening the sealed data, the customer accepts the validity of these conditions explicitly. If any provision of these Conditions be or become invalid, shall not affect the legal validity of the remaining provisions. Also reserves the right at all times HHO FACTORY, LTD modifications of these Terms and Conditions.  

Amending this Terms and conditions: HHO FACTORY, LTD may choose to change the Policy, in part or its entirety, at any time, without notice.  

Privacy Policy  
This privacy policy discloses you how we use personal information collected at this site. Our policy is to keep the personal information we receive from our site completely confidential and used solely for internal purposes.   

We will not share your personal information with any other parties.   

This Privacy Policy only applies to information collected by HHO FACTORY, LTD websites  
Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the HHO FACTORY, LTD websites.   

On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information (e.g Name, Address Email address e.t.c) collected at these pages will be held with the utmost care and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to.   

All collected information is retained for order processing and customer service only.  

During your use of our website, we will collect non-identifying personal information to enhance the functionality of the website and to make your access more convenient and efficient. We retain non-identifying personal information and use it to establish website activity trends, monitor website performance, improve website design and functionality, fulfill orders, inform current and potential customers and suppliers about our services, and for other business purposes.   

Our collection of non-identifying personal information may involve the use of cookies. Among other uses, cookies allow us to deliver content specific to your interests, to save you from re-entering your registration data at each connection, and to provide features such as online customer payment and shopping carts.   

A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of HHO FACTORY, LTD websites.  
Use VISA MASTER, AMERICAN, EXPRESS, DISCOVER, DIRECT DEBIT for purchasing operations. They are the authorized online retailer of our products.  

We will ask customers to supply various personal data when placing an order, such as name and address, credit card information, and e-mail address. HHO FACTORY, LTD have their own Privacy Policy that explains how your information is processed and protected. All non-personally-identifying information and personally identifying information described above is stored on restricted database servers.  

THIS WARRANTY IS VOID IF THE PRODUCT IS OPENED, ALTERED OR DAMAGED  

Safety Warning  

The amount of hydrogen produced on demand is small but please note the following:  
CAUTION!  Hydrogen is a flammable gas and can form explosive mixtures with oxygen or air. Hydrogen gas poses an immediate fire and explosive hazard when concentrations exceed 4%.  It is much lighter than air and burns with an invisible flame. Before working on an installed HHO system ensure to extinguish all sources of ignition, naked heat including sparks or flames disconnect the vehicles battery terminals and take precautions to eliminate static electricity.  No smoking near the generator or its reservoirs at any time. HHO generators produce HHO gases on demand when the engine is running but when disconnected there will be residual amounts of HHO gases in reservoirs and tubing.  Allow units to vent thoroughly outdoors or in a well-ventilated area before working on the units or accessories.  

Buyers should read all warnings, instructions on safe use, labels, disclaimers, and all other materials included with products sold on this website prior to using any such product. Hydrogen Generators are sold on the understanding that the buyer reads and adheres to the PRECAUTIONS AND WARNINGS OF SAFETY described in the installation in order to avoid risks. HHO FACTORY, LTD does not accept liability for damages or injuries or for any direct or consequential loss caused by the improper use, alteration of units or maintenance of HHO-generators or accessories.   

HHO FACTORY, LTD may change Privacy Policy from time to time. All changes will be affected on this page. If you have any questions about this policy or our site in general, please contact us.  

HHO FACTORY, LTD (IRELAND - EUROPE) takes your privacy seriously.  

HHO FACTORY, LTD  
ARIGNA VIEW  
2 Furnace Hill  
CARRICKNABRACK  
DRUMSHANBO  
CO. LEITRIM. N41V2K7  
IRELAND  
Tel: +353 833 111 644  
Email: [[email protected]](https://hhokit.ie/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  
Website: www.HHOFACTORY.com
